坚定留下的忠心
Steadfast devotion to stay
没有离去的念头
Without temptation to stray
永远是如此迅速
Always in motion so high
目的地只有一个
One destination to find
从空中俯瞰
Eyeing from the air
与五花八门的鸟一起
with one of every avian
底下的大地
down below at earth
和大地之上
and those upon
无数选择中
Out of such a choice,
无数噪音中
out of all the noise
只有少数会
Only few will be
被他记得
in mind of one
只有少数会
Few can belong
坚定留下的忠心
Steadfast devotion to stay
没有离去的念头
Without temptation to stray
永远是如此迅速
Always in motion so high
目的地只有一个
One destination to find
是我的荣幸
Pleasure's mine to be
能服务我的朋友
in service of a friend to me
我唯一的梦想
'Tis my only dream
以及使命
and destiny
常常我觉得
Often times I feel
如此不中用
so inadequate
除了家人外
Who am I to you
我还是什么？
but family?
噢，帮我看清
Oh help me see
帮我看清
Help me see
噢，帮我看清
Oh, help me see
帮我看清
Help me see
坚定留下的忠心
Steadfast devotion to stay
没有离去的念头
Without temptation to stray
永远是如此迅速
Always in motion so high
目的地只有一个
One destination to find